gotitapp.co 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | got it! - On Demand Platform for Knowledge

Last Revised: September 24, 2015

### Welcome to GotIt!!

GotIt! provides an educational service platform connecting “Students” and “Experts” via the GotIt! website (the “Site”), the GotIt! application (the “App”) and related Internet services (collectively, the “Service(s)”). The Service is operated by Tutor Universe Inc. (the “Company”, “we” or “us”) for users of the Service (“you”). This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy with respect to information that is collected from visitors to the Site and users of the App and/or the Services.

### Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect information from you, as further described below:

**Information You Volunteer:** We collect information from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you register for access to the Services or use certain Services. The information we collect may include but not be limited to your name, email address, grade level, gender, profile photo, and any messages, images or other content you send via the Services.

**Other Information:**

  * **_Data We Collect Automatically:_** When you interact with us through the Services, we receive and store certain information, such as an IP address, device ID, and your activities within the Services, using various technologies such as “cookies.” Cookies are data files that are transferred to a user’s computer and are intended to identify that computer. We may use cookies to remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Service. We may store the information we collect or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers.

**_Aggregated Information:_** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, we may conduct research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

  * **_Third Party Services_** : We may allow third party service providers to use cookies or similar technologies to collect information about your browsing and other usage activities over time and across different websites. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how Google uses this data, please go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). In addition, we use Mixpanel Analytics, an analytics service provided by Mixpanel, Inc. (“Mixpanel”). For more information on how Mixpanel uses this data, please go to <https://mixpanel.com/terms>. To opt out of the use of Mixpanel Analytics with respect to your data, please go to <https://mixpanel.com/optout>. We also use Kochava Analytics, an analytics service provided by Kochava, Inc. (“Kochava”). For more information on how Kochava uses this data, please go to <https://www.kochava.com/privacy-policy>.

  * **Advertising** : We may also implement features from partners for various advertising purposes. Visitors can opt out of each of the following third party providers by using the following links: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed.

  * We may (and we may allow third party service providers to) use cookies or other technologies to collect information about your browsing activities over time and across different websites following your use of the Services. Please note that the Services currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals and operate as described in this Privacy Policy whether or not a DNT signal is received.

### Where Information is Processed

The Company is based in the United States. No matter where you are located, you consent to the processing and transferring of your information in and to the U.S. and other countries. The laws of the U.S. and other countries governing data collection and use may not be as comprehensive or protective as the laws of the country where you live.

### Our Use of Your Information

We use information that you provide or that we otherwise collect in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Notably, we will use your information to link you with the best match of Expert (if you are a Student) or Student (if you are an Expert). In addition, if you are an Expert we may use your information to audit your work, build Expert rankings and facilitate payment to you; if you are a Student we may use your information to notify you of communications from Experts and other Students as well as invites from friends and to collect payment from you.

If you provide information for a certain reason, we may use that information in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the information you provide including your email address, to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide information in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your information to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. The Company and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may also use your information collected through the Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. The Company and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

The Company is not in the business of selling your information. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * **Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, your information may be part of the transferred assets.

  * **Related Companies:** We may also share your information with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

  * **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:** Like many businesses we sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Such functions include facilitating communication, mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. For example, we currently use Amazon Web Services and other data storage providers to store data related to and used in connection with the Service, which includes your information. In addition, we use Apple, Braintree/PayPal and other third party payment processors in connection with the Service. We also use Asana to enable communication among our team members. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

  * **Legal Requirements:** We may disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company or Related Companies, (iii) protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

### Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected by us other than information collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

### Children

The Services are not intended for individuals under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any information through the Services or access or use the Services in any way.

### Links to Other Web Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by us (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**_Integrating Social Networking Services_** :

One of the special features of the Service is that it allows you to enable or log in to the Services via various social networking services like Facebook or Twitter (“Social Networking Service(s)”). By directly integrating these services, we make your online experiences richer and more personalized. To take advantage of this feature, we will ask you to log into or grant us permission via the relevant Social Networking Service. When you add a Social Networking Services account to the Service or log into the Service using your Social Networking Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Social Networking Service and your data contained within that Social Networking Service. As part of such integration, the Social Networking Service will provide us with access to certain information that you have provided to the Social Networking Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Networking Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such third parties, and we shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Social Networking Services that may be enabled within the Service.

You may also have the option of posting your Services activities to Social Networking Services when you access content through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you performed an activity on the Service); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers and subscribers on any Social Networking Services you have enabled will be able to view such activity.

### Security

We take reasonable steps to protect the information provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any information via the Internet.

### Access to and Deletion of Information

To keep your information accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below with any updates or corrections to your information. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct information in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Services. Please note that while you may delete messages that you send, your username and associated information (for example, your email address) will remain stored on our servers unless and until you specifically request that we delete your information.

In order to request deletion of your information, please contact us at legal@gotitapp.co

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any personal information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### Contacting Us

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Services.

You may contact us as follows:

Mailing address:

GotIt!  
1901 S Bascom Ave, Suite 1180,  
Campbell,  
CA 95008 

Email address: legal@gotitapp.co
